{"system": "Naive Bayes", "predictions": [{"train": "hr500k.json (train split)", "test": "hr500k.json (test split)", "predictions": ["B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-loc", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-loc", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-loc", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "I-misc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-loc", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "O", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "O", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "I-org", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-deriv-per", "B-der